那解药呢  肯定有解药的
What about an antidote? There has to be an antidote.
仅存的那瓶解药和毒剂一起被盗了
The only existing vial was stolen with the toxin.
他们还能生产更多  对吧
They can make more, right?
他们肯定能生产更多
They have to be able to make more.
需要很长的时间才能合成
It would take too long to synthesize.
-多长的时间  -一周
- How long? - A week.
太长了
That's too long.
你确定我中毒了吗  我是说  我
Are you sure I was exposed? I mean, I--
我觉得没事  也许他们搞错了
I feel fine. Maybe they were... wrong.
沃特·里德医院派来了一名医生
Look, there's a doctor coming in from Walter Reed.
他会回答你提出的
He's gonna be able to answer any other questions
别的问题
that you might have.
你已经回答了
Yeah, well, I think you already did that.
别消沉
Hey.
我们会找到幕后黑手
We're gonna find whoever's behind this.
找到后  我们会拿到解药
And when we do, we're gonna get that antidote,
因为我不会让你这么轻易就抛下我这个未婚妻
'cause I'm not letting you out of our engagement that easily.
好吧
All right.
你们调查得怎么样了
So where are you in the investigation?
我们在调查一切可能的线索
We're looking into every possible lead.
你们毫无进展时就会这样说
That's what you say when you're nowhere.
卡塞尔
Castle--
绑架我的人
The guy who abducted me--
-布朗森  -对
- Yeah. Bronson. - Right.
他是军方的人  还是特工
Was he military? Special ops?
海军陆战队侦察队的  怎么了
Marine force recon. Why?
在他临终前  他说了几句话
Okay, because before he died, he said something.
瓦尔基里  我们在调查
Valkyrie. Yeah. We've been looking into it.
-但数据库里没有相关资料  -不是那个
- There's nothing in the databases. - Not that.
他说的是梦乡
He said something about dreamworld.
开始我以为那是随口乱说的
Now I didn't think it was anything,
但根据埃斯波西托的说法
but according to Esposito,
梦乡是位于中东地区的特别行动
"Dreamworld" is the code name of a special ops ghost base
幽灵基地的代号
somewhere in the Middle East.
你觉得那和盗窃毒剂的人
And you think that that somehow relates
有关系
to the theft of the toxin?
我觉得布朗森认为有关
I... think Bronson thought it did.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
我是戈德伯格医生  来为卡塞尔先生做检查
I'm Dr. Goldberg, here to check on Mr. Castle.
他怎么样
How's he doing?
比我好  调查得怎么样了
Better than I am. Where are we?
我们现在知道幕后黑手
Well, we know whoever's behind this
陷害了杰克·布朗森非法闯入
framed Jack Bronson for the break-in
然后使用毒剂杀了他
and then used the toxin to kill him.
也就是说他们得和他有交集
Which means they would have had to have crossed paths with him
-才能做到这一切  -正是
- in order to deliver it. - Exactly.
亨德里克斯和他的小队在回顾
Hendricks and his team are retracing
布朗森的一举一动  来查明人物和时间
all of Bronson's movements to get a who and a when.
这是大海捞针  但也许我们会走运
It's a needle in a haystack, but maybe we'll get lucky.
-查到瓦尔基里了吗  -没有和这事有联系的
- Anything on Valkyrie? - Nothing that connects.
但是分析员仍在查找
Analysts are still working on it, though.
你听过叫"梦乡"的东西吗
Have you ever heard of something called dreamworld?
梦乡是什么
What's dreamworld?
磷定和阿托品
The pralidoxime and atropine
会延缓毒效
will stave off the effect of the toxin
给你争取到更多时间
and buy you some more time.
多少时间
How much more?
一小时  也许两小时
An hour, maybe two.
每四小时我会给你注射一剂
I'll give you another shot every four hours,
但最终药剂会失效
but eventually it won't be effective.
那时候会怎样
And then what?
临终之时  你会觉得虚弱无力
Towards the end, you'll start to feel weak,
呼吸急促
experience shortness of breath.
为什么布朗森那么快就死了  而我还活着
Why did Bronson die so quickly, and I'm still alive?
布朗森在车里待了好几个小时
Bronson was in the car for hours,
所以他吸收了大部分毒剂
so he got the mother lode.
你在车里才待了几分钟
You were in the car just for a few minutes.
如果以液体形式摄入  你几秒钟就会死
Ingested in liquid form, you go down in seconds,
但基于你的血液检查
but based on your blood work,
你至少还能活10到12小时
you have at least another 10 to 12 hours.
那么
So then...
除开我即将死去的事实  我还好
apart from the fact that I'm dying, I'm fine?
你现在还没出现症状
You're asymptomatic.
我会尽量让你保持这样的
I'll try to keep you that way for as long as possible.
中东地区的幽灵基地
A ghost base in the Middle East?
我知道希望渺茫
Look, I know this is a long shot,
但是布朗森也许是想传递信息
but Bronson may have been trying to communicate a message.
或者是临死之人的胡言乱语
Or it's just the ramblings of a dying man.
我们查看过政府
Look, we checked the government
和军方的数据库
and military databases.
官方没有提及过梦乡
There's no official reference to dreamworld--
还不知道它存不存在呢
If it even exists.
我觉得它存在
Uh, I think it exists.
你查到了什么
What did you find?
五角大楼的档案文件里找到关键词
A name just popped in a Pentagon archive.
布拉德·帕克  《华盛顿联盟》的记者
Brad Parker, a reporter for "The Washington Union".
记者和这有什么关系
What's a reporter got to do with this?
六个月前他试图发表一篇
Six months ago he tried to publish an article
名为《揭秘梦乡》的文章
called "Inside dreamworld",
出于国家安全考虑  文章被封杀了
but it was quashed over national security concerns.
内容是什么
What does the article say?
我拿不到原文  内容被加密了
I don't have the text. They've classified it.
只能看到标题
I have the title.
我去联系五角大楼的熟人
I'll call my contact at the pentagon
看看他能查到什么
and see what he can dig up.
与此同时  找到这名记者
In the meanwhile, track down this reporter.
看他知道些什么
Find out what he knows.
你可以查一下布朗森的通话记录
You could also check Bronson's phone records.
他和这名记者可能联系过
He and this reporter might be connected.
卡塞尔  你该去休息
Castle, you should be resting.
很明显...以后有的是时间休息
There's plenty of time for that later... apparently.
如果结局不能改变  我宁愿来帮忙
Um, if it's all the same, I'd rather be helping.
卡塞尔先生  我知道你想帮忙  但是
Mr. Castle, I understand your desire to be involved, but--
没人比我更想侦破这个案子
No one is more motivated than me to solve this,
如果破不了案
and if it doesn't work out,
我就死掉了  不会再打扰你们
I'll... be out of your hair by the end of the day.
长官  卡塞尔是唯一
Y-you know, sir, Castle is the only one
与布朗森有亲身接触的人
that has firsthand experience with Bronson.
他也许能帮上忙
He might be an asset.
好吧
Okay.
贝克特探员  他由你负责
But, Agent Beckett, he's your responsibility.
好的
I know.
长官  布朗森与这名记者联系过
Sir, it looks like Bronson and the reporter are connected.
他的通话记录显示
His phone records show calls to and from
在文章写就前后
"The Washington Union"
有来自《华盛顿联盟》的电话进出
around the time the article was written.
布朗森一定是文章的线人之一
Bronson must have been a source for the article.
去  看看他知道些什么
Go. Find out what he knows.
卡塞尔先生
Uh, Mr. Castle.
你可以协助  但不能离开这栋楼
You can assist us, but only from inside this building.
好的
Right. Mm.
谢谢你在卡塞尔这件事上支持我
Look, uh, thanks for backing me up with Castle.
他总是那么有个性吗
Was he always such a character?
是啊  这也是我爱他的一个原因
Yeah. It's one of the things that I love about him, too.
来了
There.
帕克先生
Mr. Parker!
帕克先生  请留步
Mr. Parker, excuse me.
我们是司法部的探员
We're from the attorney general's office.
关于你写的《揭秘梦乡》这篇文章
We need to ask you a few questions
有几个问题想问你
about an article you wrote-- "Inside dreamworld."
真的  还要问吗
Really? We're gonna do this again?
你们简直难以置信
You people are unbelievable.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你们封杀我的文章时我没公布我的线人
I wouldn't give up my sources when you killed the article,
现在我何必透露给你们
so why would I give them up now?
因为其中一位被谋杀了
Because it looks like one of your sources was murdered.
你认识他吗  帕克先生
Do you recognize him, Mr. Parker?
布朗森
Bronson.
他被杀了
He was murdered?
是的  其他人的生命也面临威胁
Yes, and now other people's lives are at stake.
告诉我们关于梦乡你所知的一切
Now tell us everything you know about dreamworld.
我第一次听说梦乡是在03年
First time I heard about dreamworld was in '03.
当时我在驻坎大哈173师服役
I was serving with the 173rd in Kandahar at the time.
我一直记得这个故事
The story stuck with me,
大约一年前我开始四处打探
so about a year ago I started poking around.
发现梦乡是个位于阿富汗北部的
Found out it was a forward operating base
前方作战基地
in northern Afghanistan,
是该区域开展机密特别行动的控制中心
launching pad for covert special ops in the region.
布朗森在这个基地工作吗
Did Bronson work at that base?
是的
Yeah.
我听过几次他的名字
Yeah, I'd heard his name a couple of times,
所以联系了他
so I approached him.
他告诉你什么了
And what'd he tell you?
什么也没说
Nothing at all.
事实上  他看上去很惊慌
In fact, he seemed pretty freaked out
得知我知道他曾在梦乡驻扎
that I knew he was stationed there...
他问我知道多少
Asking me how much I knew...
关于他  梦乡
About him, dreamworld...
以及他做了什么
About what he'd done.
等等  你什么意思
Wait, what--what did he mean by that?
他从未提及
He never told me.
无论是什么
Whatever it was,
他肯定不想将它公开
he sure as hell didn't want it getting out.
然后我的主编得到了国防部长里德的
Next thing I know, my editor's killing the story...
个人请求  把我的文章封杀了
at the personal request of defense secretary Reed.
在你与布朗森的谈话中
These conversations that you had with Bronson--
他提到过"瓦尔基里"吗
Did he ever mention the word "Valkyrie"?
没有  怎么了  瓦尔基里是什么
No. Why? What's valkyrie?
等等
Wait.
国防部长亲自打电话
The secretary of defense himself
要求封杀文章
called to kill the story?
真很不寻常
That's unusual.
是前所未闻
Try unheard of.
我猜文章内容太过敏感
But I'm guessing that the subject matter struck a nerve.
在担任国防部长之前
Look, prior to his appointment as secretary of defense,
里德部长是总指挥官
General Reed was in charge of Central Command,
负责指挥梦乡的所有对外任务
which ran all missions out of dreamworld.
你是说国防部长
Are you suggesting that the secretary of defense
有所隐瞒
is hiding something?
有其他的解释吗
You have another explanation?
一瓶失窃的军用毒剂
So a stolen military toxin
和一个政府秘密基地有关
and a secret government base.
这究竟是怎么回事
I mean, what do you think this is all about?
我不知道  但我感觉布朗森知情
I don't know, but I have a feeling Bronson did.
我们去哪儿
Where are we headed?
去和那个唯一知道
To talk to the one person who might actually
发生什么事的人谈谈
know what's going on.
梦乡的前指挥官
Former commander of dreamworld--
国防部长里德
Defense Secretary Reed.
部长先生
Mr. Secretary.
司法部长亲自请我会见你们
This must be damned important if the Attorney General's
希望这是十万火急的事
personally asking me to take this meeting.
确实
It is.
三天前  一种致命毒剂失窃于
Three days ago, a lethal toxin was stolen
一个政府实验室
from a government lab.
我们的调查指向
Our investigations led us to the murder
前海军士兵杰克·布朗森的谋杀案
of an ex-marine named Jack Bronson.
-您认识他吗  -有可能
- Do you know him? - It's possible.
很多人曾服役于我的手下
A lot of men served under my command.
怎么  你们认为他和失窃案有关
Why? You think he was involved in this theft?
不  但他可能知道是谁
No, but he may have known who was.
我们认为这和
We believe that this is connected
一个叫做梦乡的军事基地有关
to a military base named Dreamworld.
我不想扫兴  但梦乡只是传奇
Well, I hate to break it to you, but Dreamworld's a myth.
它是军事传奇  但并不存在
It's military legend. It doesn't exist.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
-你真的要玩这种把戏吗  -长官
- Are we actually gonna play this game? - Sir--
贝克特探员  是吗
Agent Beckett, was it?
不管毒剂在谁手里  只要他们使用
Whoever took that toxin, if they use it,
就会出现大面积的伤亡
there will be mass casualties,
-如果你知道什么  -长官
- so if you know something-- - Sir.
有人写过关于梦乡的文章
Someone was writing an article about Dreamworld.
你亲自把封掉了  为什么
You personally had that story killed. Why?
为什么  因为敌人也读报纸
Why? Because the enemy reads newspapers,
我不可能冒着美国人民的性命危险
and there's no way in hell I'm gonna risk American lives
把特别行动基地的
by handing out operational details
行动细节交出去
about a special ops base...
如果这种基地存在的话
If such a base existed.
布朗森呢
What about Bronson?
他和基地有什么联系
What's his connection to that base?
如果它存在的话
If it indeed does exist.
我即将要说的每句话都不能记录在案
Everything I'm about to say is off the books.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
-明白  -明白
- Yes. - Yes.
布朗森是名杰出的海军陆战队员
Bronson was an outstanding marine.
但是他只负责一个任务
But he only worked one mission out of there--
一个在贾拉拉巴德的空袭
A high-value air strike in Jalalabad
目的是除掉基地组织二号头目阿瓦·扎瓦利
that took out Anwar Zawari-- Al-Qaeda's number two.
布朗森负责哪个部分
What was Bronson's role?
他是我们的地面接应人员
He was our man on the ground.
埋伏在附近的楼里
Set up in a nearby building.
扎瓦利进去的时候他向上级报告
He reported when Zawari went in the house.
当空袭启动的时候
Then, when the air strike was launched,
他用激光指向房子
he painted the house with a laser
指引导弹
to guide the missile.
瓦尔基里这个词
Did the word "Valkyrie"
和空袭有关吗
have anything to do with this strike?
是任务名还是暗号
Was it the name of a mission or a code name?
不是
No.
没听过
It's not familiar.
那次行动的成功对我们来说意义重大
Look, that operation was a big win for us.
重创了基地组织的整个指挥部门
It crippled Al-Qaeda's entire command structure.
有没有听说基地组织要报复
Was there any talk of Al-Qaeda retaliating?
有谣言  一直都有
There was chatter. Always is.
但是我们一年前就除掉了扎瓦利
But we took out Zawari a year ago,
但他们从未回击
and they never hit us back.
只不过他们开始回击了
Unless they just did.
而且只是开始
And this is just the beginning.
我让国土安全局看紧每个
I have Homeland tightening security
在特区的潜在目标
at every likely D.C. target--
政府大楼  景点  交通枢纽
Government buildings, tourist attractions, transit hubs.
坏消息是毒剂传播途径太多
The bad news is the toxin's versatile.
可以放置在通风装置里
It can be deployed through the ventilation system,
可以投进水库
it could contaminate a reservoir,
放在炸弹里引爆
it can be detonated with a bomb
毒气飘在城市上空
and release a toxic plume over part of this city.
如果这样的话  我们就不止要处理
And if that happens, we'd be dealing with a lot more
一两个死亡案件了
than just a couple of deaths on our hands.
实在对不起
And I am so sorry.
没事  这是你的工作
No, it's... your job.
如果我们阻止下次袭击  也许可以救我
And if we stop the next attack, it might mean saving me.
但如果这是基地组织的报复
But if this is Al-Qaeda retaliation,
他们是怎么知道布朗森的
how did they know about Bronson?
那次空袭他是地面接应人员
He was on the ground during the air strike.
他可能被当地人
He might have been seen by locals
或者扎瓦利家里人看见了
or Zawari family members.
我们去查在特区的
Well, let's check for any Zawari family members,
扎瓦利家人  朋友或者与其有关的人
friends, or associates in the D.C. area.
如果基地组织要反击
If Al-Qaeda is about to strike,
他们一定有线人在这边
they must have people on the ground.
我去技术室
I'll be in the tech room.
我没事
Look-- I'm okay.
我
I...
是我妈妈  她一直在给我打电话
It's my mother. She's been calling all morning.
我不能一直躲着她
I can't, uh, avoid her forever.
你好啊  妈妈
Hello, mother.
-怎么想起给我打电话啊  -理查德
- To what do I owe the pleasure? - Richard.
你昨晚像个罪犯一样
You were ushered out of here last night
被人带走
like a common criminal.
你又不接我电话  到底怎么了
You don't answer my calls. What the hell is going on?
没事  妈妈  我没事
No--mother, I'm--I'm fine.
爸爸  他们逮捕你了吗
Dad, did they arrest you?
要我们去保释你吗
Do you need us to bail you out?
不如请个律师吧   C先生
Ooh! What about a lawyer, Mr. C?
我在美国公民自由协会认识个律师
I know a guy at the ACLU
天啊
Oh, please.
不用了
No.
我恰巧有关于贝克特在处理的案子
Uh, I just had some, uh, special knowledge
特殊知识
of a case that Beckett's working on.
她是派人来护送我的
She had them send an escort, that's all.
谢天谢地
Oh. Well, thank God.
吉娜今早打过来
Um... oh, Gina called this morning.
她有些书让你签名
She has, uh, a bunch of books for you to sign
送给公司的贵宾
for some company VIPs.
是
Right. Um...
在我书房  后面那个书架
They're in my office at the, uh, back bookcase.
如果我...
If I'm...
如果我明天没回去
If I'm not there tomorrow,
让她直接拿走
she can come pick them up.
妈妈
And, mother...
谢谢你
Thank you.
他什么时候回来
When's he coming back?
让我和阿丽克西斯说
Let me talk to Alexis.
他想和你说  亲爱的
He wants to talk to you, honey.
爸爸
Hey, dad.
我明天应该就能回来了
Hopefully I'll be back tomorrow morning.
你知道我爱你的  对吗
You know I love you, right?
当然了
Of course.
是时候打下一针了
It's time for your next shot.
这么快
Already?
爸爸  还好吗
Dad? Everything okay?
他们在叫我
Yeah. They're calling me,
我要挂电话了
so I have to go.
好
Okay.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
好  明天见
Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow.
有没有觉得爸爸很奇怪
Did dad sound weird to you?
长官  有发现
Sir, we've got something.
看来你对扎瓦利家族的猜测是对的
Turns out you were right about Zawari's family.
我们查到他们家族中的六名成员
We identified six members of his extended family
都住在美国
living in the U.S.--
四人住在加州
Four in California
两个表亲就住在特区
and two cousins right here in D.C.
我们在调查他们的时候
We were in the process of running them down
亨德里克斯找到了这个
when Hendricks found this.
重现布朗森生前的活动路线
In reconstructing Bronson's movements prior to his death,
我们追踪到了这里
we were able to track him to here,
杜邦环岛的一家咖啡店
a coffee shop in Dupont Circle.
他前脚刚离开
A few seconds after he leaves,
这个人立马跟了出来
this man follows him out.
我们确认他叫瓦卡斯·拉希德
We've I.D.'d him as Waqas Rasheed,
扎瓦利的远房表亲
second cousin to Zawari.
里奇蒙德探员正在尝试找他
And Agent Richmond is trying to track him down,
但我们了解到
but here's what we know--
他有美国和阿富汗的双重国籍
he has dual U.S./Afghan citizenship,
乔治城大学工程学毕业
is a graduate engineering student at Georgetown.
长官  在夜袭扎瓦利时
And, sir, he was in Jalalabad
他就在贾拉拉巴德
the night of the Zawari air strike.
其他五个表亲都在袭击中丧生
Five of his other cousins were killed in the attack.
家里死了这么多人
Burying that many family members,
足以激起任何人的报复欲
that could radicalize anyone.
找到了  找到他了
Got him. We got him.
找到了拉希德的实时位置
We have a live feed of Rasheed
在14街E和F路之间向东走
walking east on 14th Street bewteen "E" and "F".
-双肩包  -可能装着毒剂
- Backpack. - Could be the toxin.
-和解药  -行动
- And the antidote. - Let's move!
站住  站住
Stop! Stop!
联邦探员  站住
Federal agents! Stop!
不在包里
It's not here.
毒剂在哪
Where's the toxin?
拉希德  毒剂在哪
Rasheed! Where's the toxin?
他不开口怎么办
What if he doesn't talk?
他会开口的  嫌犯都这样
He'll talk. They always do.
如果他没及时交待呢
What if he doesn't talk in time?
已经派人搜查他的住处了
We have teams combing his apartment.
如果他有毒剂和解药  会找到的
If he has the toxin and the antidote, they'll find 'em.
谢谢你
Thanks...
让我参与这次行动
for letting me be a part of this.
你在写下一部小说的时候
When you write your next novel,
不妨写一写
maybe you'll find a place
一位英俊勇猛的哥伦比亚裔联邦探员
for a dashing Colombian-American federal agent.
包在我身上
Consider it done.
在拉希德家里找到什么了吗
Anything at Rasheed's?
我们翻遍了所有角落
We went over every inch of his place,
都没找到解药和毒剂
and there is no sign of the antidote or the toxin.
他可能将其藏在某处
He may have hidden it somewhere.
不然就是已经布置好
Either that or it's already out there,
准备投放了
ready to be deployed.
撬开他的嘴
Break him.
为什么抓我
So why am I here?
这都是怎么回事
What's this about? Huh?
你跟阿瓦·扎瓦利是亲戚  对不对
You're related to Anwar Zawari. Is that correct?
人无法选择自己的家庭
A man doesn't choose his family.
阿瓦和他的信仰都与我无关
Okay? I had nothing to do with Anwar or his beliefs.
但是他死掉当晚你在贾拉拉巴德
Yet you were in Jalalabad the night that he died.
是  但不是去见他  我有亲戚在那儿
Yes, but not to see him. I have relatives there.
我跟他们一起过斋月
I was spending time with them for Ramadan.
我了解到你的五个亲戚
I understand that five of your relatives
在美方导弹袭击中丧生
were killed in that U.S. Missile strike.
所以我把这归咎于阿瓦  是他们要跟着他
And for that I blame Anwar, and them for being with him.
为什么抓我到这儿
Now why am I here?
你是学工程的
You studied engineering.
确切地说  是电气系统设计
Specifically, electrical system designs
用于商业建筑
for commercial buildings.
你真有本事把所有事都说得那么邪恶
You have a gift for making every fact sound sinister.
你有能力侵入机密工厂
Well, you'd be able to break into a secure facility.
我没有闯入任何建筑
I didn't break into anything.
我要见律师  我有权见律师
I want an attorney. I have a right to an attorney.
政府公敌没有律师  或者审判
Enemy combatants don't get attorneys... or trials.
毒剂在哪  拉希德
Where is the toxin, Rasheed?
我不知道你们在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我认为你知道  事实上我确认你知道
I think you do. In fact, I know you do.
这是杰克·布朗森  前海军陆战队员
This is Jack Bronson, former U.S. Marine.
袭击当晚他在贾拉拉巴德
He was in Jalalabad the night of the strike.
而这
And this...
是你  跟着他出了咖啡店
is you, following him outside of a coffee shop.
三小时后  他死了
Three hours later, he was dead.
别跟我说这是什么巧合
You're not gonna tell me that that's a coincidence.
是因为他吗
This is about him?
你们搞错了
Well, you have it wrong.
我没有跟踪他
I wasn't following him.
是他在跟踪我
He was following me.
他为什么要跟踪你
Why would he be following you?
他想知道我有没有把我们之间的秘密
He wanted to know if I talked to anybody...
告诉别人
about our secret.
你们之间的秘密
Your secret?
什么秘密
What secret?
导弹袭击那晚
The night of the missile strike,
我在我哥家
I was, uh, at my brother's home.
离阿瓦家只有一个街区
It's just a block away from Anwar's.
我听到爆炸声  跑了出去
I heard the explosion. I ran out.
房子炸毁了  我是第一个赶到的
The house was destroyed. And I was the first one there,
所以我去看看有没有幸存者
so I wanted to see if there were any survivors.
那时
And that's, uh...
那时我看到了布朗森
that's when I saw Bronson,
站在废墟中  抱着一具尸体
standing there in the rubble, holding a body.
是谁
Whose body?
一个年轻女子
A young woman.
是一个女仆
One of the servants in the house.
当他看到我的时候  他...
And when he saw me, he...
举起枪
drew his gun.
我觉得自己必死无疑了
And I thought for sure I was a dead man.
但他说话了
But then he spoke.
他知道我的名字
And he knew my name
我的住处  我的工作
and where I lived and what I did.
他还说如果我告诉别人我看到的事
And he told me that if I told anyone about what I had seen,
就杀了我
he would kill me.
然后他走了
And then he left...
抱着那具尸体
with the body.
他带走了一个女仆的尸体
He took away a dead servant's body?
我尽力忘记这件事
I've done my best to forget about it all,
直到他在咖啡店找到我
until he found me in the coffee shop,
他不停地问我  你还告诉谁了
and he kept asking me, "Who did you tell?
他们为什么陷害我  我对他发誓
Why are they setting me up?" And I swore to him
我没有告诉任何人
I didn't tell anybody.
无论现在发生什么事情  什么情况
Okay, whatever is happening here, whatever is going on,
我发誓和我一点关系都没有
I swear to you I have nothing to do with it.
没有任何情报组织能把拉希德
So none of the intelligence agencies can link Rasheed
和已知基地组织联系在一起
to known Al-qaeda elements.
而且
And...
他在劫案发生当晚有可靠的不在场证明
He's got a solid alibi for the night of the break-in.
那他也有参与的可能
He could still be involved.
有没有关于近期即将发生袭击的消息
Is there any chatter about an imminent attack?
没什么异常
No more than usual.
你对拉希德有何看法
What's your take on Rasheed?
我觉得他不是我们要找的人
I don't think he's our guy.
基于什么
Base on?
他的故事  他说他看见布朗森
His story. I mean, he said that he saw Bronson
在转移女仆的尸体
carrying a servant girl's body.
我觉得他能想出
I mean, the only way that he'd come up
这样的故事  只能是因为他亲眼所见
with a story like that was if it was true.
所以说除了"瓦尔基里"
So aside from the name "Valkyrie," which no one we've spoken to
这个我们讯问过的人都不知道的名字
seems to know anything about,
我们基本一无所获  而我必死无疑
we pretty much have nothing, which means I'm a dead man.
不  卡塞尔  不是一无所获
No, Castle. Not nothing.
我们有布朗森和你说的话  拉希德告诉我们的情况
We have what Bronson told you, what Rasheed told us.
我们知道这一切都围绕着
We know that this revolves around something
扎瓦利被杀当晚的事件展开的
that happened the night Zawari was killed,
而这件事不止是空袭那么简单
something more than just the air strike.
我们现在只要搞清楚这件事是什么
Now what we have to do is figure out what it was.
我已经让国防部发来了任务文件
I'll have D.O.D. send over the mission documents.
或许会对我们有所帮助
Maybe something in there will help shed some light.
这些就是任务文件
These are the mission documents?
就没有一句是完整的吗
Is there even a sentence that doesn't have redactions?
没有一句
Not a complete one.
一定是有人在试图掩盖事实真相
Somebody is definitely trying to hide whatever went on here.
抱歉  卡塞尔  这一点意义都没有
I-I'm sorry, Castle. This is pointless.
你能搜索关键词"瓦尔基里"吗
Can you do a word search for "Valkyrie"?
文件中没有出现
It doesn't appear in the document.
可能是因为被划掉了
Probably because it's redacted.
对  那搜索
Right. But what about
和英文"瓦尔基里"一样长度
a search for blacked-out 8-letter words
但被遮蔽的八个字符呢
the same length as "Valkyrie"?
八个字符的词多了去了
Aren't all 8-letter words the same length?
但这样的情况不会在新罗马体中出现
Well, not in a proportional font like Times Roman.
每个字符大小不一
Each character will vary in size
从最窄的小写"i"
from the narrowest-- a lowercase "I"--
到最宽的大写"W"
to the widest-- the uppercase "W."
所以在"瓦尔基里"一词的字母组合
So the combination of letters in the word "Valkyrie"
会产生一个特定的长度
will create a very specific length,
和印刷指纹有点像
Not unlike a typographical fingerprint.
我可以尝试一下
I may be able to work with that.
如果我们能找到被屏蔽的"瓦尔基里"
If we can find the blacked-out "Valkyrie,"
我们就能通过周围的单词
we might be able to figure out what it means
破解它的意义
from the words around it.
希望渺茫  我知道
It's a long shot, I know.
没那么渺茫  我们有发现了
Not that long. We got some hits.
这些是文件的缩略图
These are thumbnails of the whole document.
每一张上都有  用红色标出
It's everywhere, highlighted in red.
而最后一页似乎最为频繁
The last page seems to have the largest concentration.
能放大吗
Can you enlarge it?
"获取目标"  "导弹发射"
"Target acquired." "Missile engaged."
"目标摧毁"
"Target destroyed."
这是导弹袭击的文字记录稿
This is the transcript to the missile strike.
或许"瓦尔基里"是扎瓦利的代号
Maybe "Valkyrie" Is the code name for Zawari.
不  不会那么简单
No, it's got to be more than that,
但是没有足够的上下文来破解词义
but there's not enough context to piece this thing together.
我们需要的是原件
What we need is an un-redacted transcript.
或者是原始录音
Or the original audio recording.
你是怎么想的  里奇蒙德
What are you thinking, Richmond?
对于贾拉拉巴德的袭击
For a strike in Jalalabad,
可能会用到巴格拉姆空军基地的F16战斗机
They'd probably use an f-16 out of Bagram Air Base.
我曾在那里做过一年的技术主管
I did a year as chief technical officer at bagram.
工作的一部分就是将战斗机的飞行数据
Part of my job was dumping the fighter jets' flight data
存入到中央服务器中
onto a central server.
如果我能进入到服务器中
If I can access it,
我可能会拿到录音
I might be able to get that audio.
我们还等什么  麦考德
What are we waiting for, McCord?
我们照章办事  而他们就给了我们这个
We played by the rules, and that's what they gave us.
动手吧
Do it.
卡塞尔  你妈妈
Castle. It's your mom.
你想让我怎么说
What do you want me to tell her?
你已接通司法部长办公室
You've reached the voicemail of Special Agent Kate Beckett
联邦探员凯特·贝克特的语音信箱
at the Attorney General's office.
请留言
Please leave a message.
我只是一直觉得咱俩
I just always thought that you and I
会一起养个孩子
Would have kids together.
真的  你跟珍妮说过咱俩好上的事了吗
Really? Well, have you talked to Jenny about this?
你知道我的意思
No, you know what I mean.
他们会在同一个棒球橄榄球队
They'd be on the same t-ball and pop warner teams.
-我们会一起当教练  -一起
- We'd co-coach. - Co-coach?
-你想当主教练  -当然
- You want to be head coach? - Yeah.
-那就先找孩他妈  -兄弟
- Try getting a date first. - Dude.
玛莎  你怎么来了
Hey. Martha. What brings you here?
我知道你们很忙  但是我
Look, I know you're busy, but I'm--
-我很担心理查德  -真的  怎么了
- I'm worried about Richard. - Really? Why?
昨晚  他被几个
Last night, he was just whisked away
联邦探员"暴徒"给抓走了
by a couple of federal agent... thugs.
但是当我今天打给他
Then when I talked to him today,
他友好又真诚  也没有臭屁
he was nice, sincere, no smart-ass quips.
所以  一定是出事了
So... something is definitely wrong.
而凯瑟琳也不接我电话
And Katherine isn't answering my calls.
那一定是事出有因
Well, uh, I'm sure there's an explanation.
所以我需要你们查出来
And I need you to find out what it is.
有呼吸困难吗
Any trouble breathing?
是  但可能是我太焦虑了
Yeah, but I-I think that's just anxiety.
-我可以给你镇定剂  -不
- I can get you a sedative. - No.
谢谢  我还是尽量保持清醒吧
I--thank you. I think I'd rather stay sharp as long as possible.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
不  没事  我们完事了
No, no problem. We're all done here.
要咖啡吗
You want a coffee?
不  让我喝那难喝的东西还不如让我死呢
Uh, no, I'd rather die than drink any more of that sludge.
玩笑开太早了
Too soon?
麦考德探员  我能问你个问题吗
Agent McCord, Can I ask you a question?
当然
Yeah.
她在这里怎么样
How is she doing... here?
贝克特  她很好  很有潜力
Beckett? She's good. She has a lot of potential.
所以她会很好的
So she'll be okay.
她会很好的
Hey. She's gonna be great.
麦考德  我进去了
Hey, McCord. I'm in.
我把巴格拉姆的飞行记录信息库
I cross-referenced the flight recording database at bagram
和任务文件中的参数进行对比
with parameters from the mission documents.
如果信息准确
If that information was accurate,
这应该就是扎瓦利空袭的音频
this should be audio of the Zawari strike.
A1  老鹰接触到目标
Alpha One, Eagle's contact target.
收到  老鹰  奥马哈  报告情况  完毕
Copy, Eagle. Omaha, what's your status? Over.
那是国防部长里德
That's defense secretary Reed.
他是战区司令  要指挥行动的
As theater commander, he'd be running the operation.
A1  瓦尔基里仍在目标范围内
Alpha One, Valkyrie still inside target.
那是布朗森的声音
That's Bronson's voice.
那瓦尔基里一定就是扎瓦利了
So Valkyrie must be Zawari.
老鹰  准备开火
Eagle, prepare to engage.
A1  瓦尔基里仍在目标里
Alpha One, Valkyrie still inside.
正在发送信号救她出来
Signaling to get her out.
"她"  那瓦尔基里就不是扎瓦利
Get "her" Out? Valkyrie's not Zawari.
或许是仆人
Maybe it's the servant.
奥马哈  瓦尔基里得马上出来了
Omaha, Valkyrie needs to get out now.
我在发信号  A1  但是没收到回复  待命
I'm signaling, Alpha One. No response. Stand by.
我们要错失机会了
We're not missing our window.
老鹰  这里是A1  向目标开火
Eagle, this is Alpha One. Engage target.
不行  老鹰  有美国情报人员在里面
Negative, Eagle. We have an American Intelligence asset in there,
我们得等她出来
and we need to wait for her get her out.
情报人员
An intelligence asset?
再给我两分钟
Just give me two minutes.
不行  奥马哈  我们不能失去肉食鸟
Negative, Omaha. We can't risk losing Raptor.
我命令你向目标开火  完毕
On my authority, you are clear to engage target. Over.
导弹发射
Missile engaged.
不行  瓦尔基里还在里面
No! Valkyrie's still in there.
目标摧毁  老鹰回巢
Target destroyed. Eagle heading home.
奥马哈  找回瓦尔基里的尸体
Omaha, retrieve Valkyrie's body
带她回梦乡
and get her back to Dreamworld.
-飞去来协议  完毕  -收到
- Protocol boomerang. Over. - Roger.
瓦尔基里是那个女仆  她是我们的人
Valkyrie was the servant. She was one of ours.
难怪对话记录改了那么多
No wonder the transcript was so heavily redacted.
国防部长里德下令杀死了一名美国情报人员
Secretary Reed killed an American operative.
然后还让布朗森掩盖此事
And then ordered Bronson to cover it up.
导弹发射
Missile engaged.
不行  瓦尔基里还在里面
No! Valkyrie's still in there.
目标摧毁  老鹰回巢
Target destroyed. Eagle heading home.
奥马哈  找回瓦尔基里的尸体
Omaha, retrieve Valkyrie's body
带她回梦乡
and get her back to Dreamworld.
-飞去来协议  完毕  -收到
- Protocol boomerang. Over. - Roger.
那现在是什么情况
So what are we saying here?
布朗森的被杀是为了掩盖
That Bronson was murdered to cover up the death
一名美国情报人员的死
of an American operative?
同时里德将军还牵扯其中
With the implication that general Reed is behind it?
也就是当今的国防部长
The sitting secretary of defense?
他能爬到这个位子
A position he got
很大程度上是因为他成功歼灭扎瓦利
largely because of his success in taking out Zawari.
他的政治前途一片光明
His political star was on the rise.
或许他不能允许有对他不利的事泄露
Maybe he couldn't afford to have damaging details out there.
但如果他想灭布朗森的口
But if he wanted to silence Bronson,
何必那么麻烦先陷害他
why would he go through the trouble of setting him up first?
而且这一切都不能解释毒素被盗
And none of this explains the theft of the toxin.
长官  他在瓦尔基里和布朗森的事上都对我们撒谎了
Sir, he lied to us about Valkyrie and about Bronson.
这事要么与他有关
Either he's involved,
要么他也有很多事情隐瞒没说
or he knows a hell of a lot more than he's telling us.
但是你没有证据
Only you have no proof.
贝克特  我知道对于你和卡塞尔
Listen, Beckett, I know what's at stake
这事有多严重
for you and for Castle,
但是  我不能让你在没有证据的情况下去找他
but... I can't let you go at him without concrete evidence.
维尔莱迪没同意
Hey. So I'm guessing Villante said "No"
对里德部长施水刑  逼他说出实情
to the idea of waterboarding the truth out of secretary Reed.
是啊  差不多吧
Yeah. Something like that.
你还好吗
How are you feeling?
还行  我觉得我该再去打一针了
Ah. Good. I think I'm just due for another shot.
我是司法部长办公室的贝克特探员
I'm agent Beckett from the Attorney General's office.
-我要跟里德部长谈谈  -有预约吗
- I need to speak with secretary Reed. - Do you have an appointment?
不  事关国家安全
No, this is a matter of national security.
抱歉  如果你没预约...
I'm sorry. If you don't have an appointment,
-我就得请你  -我明白
- I have to ask you- - I-I understand.
请你去找一下部长
Just please get to the secretary.
我说了  此事事关国家安全
I told you, this is a matter of national--
-女士  你得退后  -里德部长
- Ma'am, you need to step back. - Secretary Reed?
-里德部长  我是贝克特探员  -退后
- Secretary Reed, agent Beckett... - Step back.
我是司法部长办公室的
from the attorney general's office.
我们今天早些时候见过  长官
We met earlier today, sir.
迈克尔  那是谁
Michael, who is that?
-我会处理的  -女士  请您退后
- I'll take care of it. - Ma'am, you need to step back
-退到您车那里  -长官  我只想跟您谈谈
- to your vehicle right now. - Sir, we just need to speak.
-此事事关国家安全  -约瑟夫
- This is a matter of national security. - Joseph.
你居然跑来我家
You show up at my home?
你以为你是谁啊
Who the hell do you think you are?
这话该我问你
I should ask you the same thing.
你对瓦尔基里的事撒谎了
You lied about Valkyrie.
你妨碍了联邦探员调查案件
You obstructed a federal investigation.
我对你已经知无不言
I told you all you need to know.
我要知道一切  到底是怎么回事
I need to know everything. What is going on,
你到底想隐藏什么
and what are you hiding?
你找错了人  探员
You are barking up the wrong tree, agent,
这会让你付出代价
And it's gonna cost ya.
现在有一种致命毒素流落在外
There's a deadly toxin out there.
如果因为你不肯合作而死了哪怕一个人
If so much as one person dies because you won't cooperate,
-那我就  -你能怎么样
- Then I- - You'll what?
不论这是怎么回事  跟我都毫无关系
Look, whatever this is, it has nothing to do with me.
别忘了战斗的第一规则
You might wanna remember the first rule of combat.
不要挑起你无法取胜的战争
You don't ever start a war you can't win.
说
What?
贝克特  是埃斯波西托和莱恩
Hey, Beckett. It's, uh, Esposito and Ryan.
你还好吗
Is everything okay?
好着呢  怎么了
Fine. Why?
卡塞尔的妈妈来过  很担心他
Castle's mom came by, all worried about him.
贝克特  说吧  到底怎么回事
Come on, Beckett. What's going on?
没事
Everything's fine.
用鼻子吸
Keep taking it in through the nose,
从嘴呼出
out through the mouth.
谢谢
Thank you again.
你到底是怎么想的
What the hell were you thinking?
长官  我只是跟着直觉走
Sir, I was just following a hunch.
下次  跟着命令走
Next time, follow orders.
我不得不去与司法部长见面
I had to go to the mat with the Attorney General
以保住你的职位
to keep your job.
等等  里德部长向司法部长投诉了
Wait. Secretary Reed complained to the Attorney General?
如果你感到惊讶  你没我想象得那么聪明
If that surprises you, you're not as smart as I thought.
不  长官  如果里德是背后主谋
No, sir, it's just, if Reed was behind this,
他不会打电话的
He wouldn't have made that call.
没错  因为他不想引火烧身
Right, because he wouldn't want to call attention to himself.
所以你才会激怒他
Is that why you went out there?
迫使他有所行动
To force him to show his hand?
厉害
I'm impressed.
厉害什么啊
Yeah, well, don't be.
唯一的嫌疑人被我排除嫌疑了
Looks like I just ruled out our only lead.
伙计们  我有线索
Guys, I got something.
我在追查瓦尔基里
I was following up on Valkyrie
想看看还有没有内幕
to see if there was anything more to the story.
我们从拉希德那里拿到一张家庭照片
This is a family photo we got from Rasheed.
他确认这个女人
He identified this woman...
是布朗森在空袭后
as the servant whose body Bronson took
带走的女仆
after the air strike.
我们确认她是法拉赫·乌斯曼
And we've identified her as Farrah Usman.
这里显示她是一名承包商
She's listed as a civilian contractor
在喀布尔的美国领事馆工作
working out of the U.S. Consulate in Kabul.
这是情报人员的典型伪装身份
It's a typical cover for an intelligence operative.
她被认为是被路边简易爆炸装置杀死
Now she was supposedly killed by a roadside I.E.D.
就是扎瓦利被空袭那晚
The same night as the Zawari attack.
这说得通
Well, that makes sense.
简易爆炸装置的伤痕与空袭造成的
The injuries from an I.E.D. look a lot like those
很像
from an air strike.
那不是关键  看这个
That's not the story. Look at this.
法拉赫·乌斯曼的尸体
So Farrah Usman's body
两天后被运回多弗尔[空军基地]
was shipped back to dover two days later
被这个人认尸
and was claimed by this man.
认出这个名字了吗
You recognize that name?
布拉德·帕克  那个记者
Brad Parker? The reporter?
就是他
One and the same.
我不明白  他跟瓦尔基里是怎么联系起来的
I don't get it. How is he connected to Valkyrie?
根据文书显示  他是她的未婚夫
According to the paperwork, he was her fiance.
他跟这一切都有关
He's involved in this whole thing.
作为实战老兵  布拉德·帕克知道
As a combat vet, Brad Parker would have known
他的未婚妻并非死于简易爆炸装置
his fiance's injuries weren't from an IED.
所以他才会报道梦乡
That's why he was doing the story on Dreamworld
并找到布朗森
and why he tracked down Bronson.
他在查明未婚妻丧命的真相
He was trying to figure out how she actually died.
他是退伍军人
And he's ex-military.
他有能力完成盗窃
He would have had the skills to pull off that heist.
也就是说
So what are we saying here?
帕克因为未婚妻的死偷走毒素
That Parker stole the toxin because of his fiance?
为了报仇
That this is about revenge?
毒素是最好的选择
Well, the toxin would be perfect for that.
致命  通过尸检又查不出来
It's deadly and undetectable via autopsy
除非你知道你要找什么
unless you're specifically looking for it.
所以他才会通过制造另一场盗窃案
Which is why he tried to hide the fact that it was stolen
和陷害布朗森
by staging the other theft in the building
来掩盖真相
and framing Bronson.
搜寻帕克  查得怎么样了
Where are we on tracking Parker?
他没上班  一整天没见到人
He's not at work. No one's seen him all day.
我得不到他的手机讯号
I can't get a trace on his cell signal.
他一定是关机了
He must have turned it off.
长官  哪怕只有一点点机会
Sir, if there's the slightest chance...
去他的公寓  行动
Hit his apartment. Go.
卡塞尔
Castle.
你待在这
You stay here.
我在不到一天之前
I was given less than a day to live
被告知只有不到一条的生命
just a little less than a day ago.
如果帕克有解药  我得跟他们一起去
If Parker has that antidote, I need to go with them.
好吧
Okay.
安全
Clear!
卧室安全
Bedroom's clear!
安全  这家伙哪去了
Clear. Where the hell is this guy?
伙计们  开始工作吧
All right, guys, let's get to work.
如果毒素或解药在这  给我找出来
If that toxin or antidote are in here, I want them found.
这些是毒素被偷走大楼
These are blueprints of the research building
的蓝图
the toxin was stolen from.
关于毒素的机密文件  帕克就是我们要找的人
And a confidential file on the toxin. Parker's our guy.
他对里德部长做了背景调查
He's got a background on Secretary Reed.
研究材料
Research materials.
里德是他的下个目标
Reed's his next target.
他要除掉那个下令
He's going after the man that gave the order
杀死他未婚妻的人
that killed his fiance.
我想我知道在哪儿
And I think I know where.
这是帕克参加里德在海军学院在演讲
This is confirmation of Parker's press credentials
的记者证确认函
for Reed's address at the naval academy.
里德在今天下午五点要给新生做演讲
Reed's talking to new cadets at 5:00 p.m. today.
那在20分钟后  我们得把里德安全保护起来
That's in 20 minutes. We gotta lock Reed down.
逮住帕克  拿到解药
Secure Parker and get that antidote.
感谢你能来  部长先生
Thanks for coming, Mr. Secretary.
是我的荣幸  约翰逊将军
It's my pleasure, Admiral Johnson.
能离开办公室挺好的
It's nice to get out of the office.
希望你别介意  咱们得先接受媒体采访
Hope you don't mind that we do the press line first.
没事的
Oh, that's fine.
要我联系戈德伯格医生
Do we want me to get ahold of Dr. Goldberg
让他到那里跟咱们碰面吗
and have him meet us there?
他已经给我打过最后一针了
He already gave me my last shot.
现在能帮到我的只有解药
The only thing that can help me now is the antidote.
海军学院的媒体部
Naval Academy's press department
说帕克还没有登记
says Parker hasn't checked in yet.
安保人员已经就位找他了
Security teams are already on site looking for him.
收到
Copy that.
说不通
Doesn't make any sense.
帕克怎么还没到
Why wouldn't Parker be there yet?
人很多
There's thousands of people there.
也许他们还没看到他
Maybe they just haven't spotted him yet.
如果不用记者证  为什么
Why go through the trouble of getting press credentials
要大费周章去办理呢
if you're not gonna use them?
除非他又摆了我们一道
Unless he's pulling another head fake.
就像加密系统
Like the encryption system
是为了偷毒素的掩护
was a cover for the theft of the toxin.
军事策略
Military tactics.
总是让我们落后一招
Always making sure we're a step behind.
落后什么
A step behind what?
我是说这一切是为了复仇
I mean, this has to be about revenge,
定是冲着里德来的
so it has to be about Reed.
也许他想以牙还牙  以眼还眼
Maybe he wants to do to Reed what Reed did to him--
杀死他最爱的人
Take away the person he loves the most.
他妻子
His wife.
贝克特  你为什么调头
Beckett, why'd you turn around?
卡塞尔不行了吗
Is it Castle?
不  我们有个想法
No. We have a hunch.
什么想法
What kind of hunch?
国防部长里德办公室
Defense Secretary Reed's office.
我是贝克特探员
This is Agent Beckett
-司法部长调查...  -请稍等
- from the Attorney General's investigative-- - Hold, please.
等等  还在吗
No, wait. Hello?
-凯特  -卡塞尔  坚持住  我们马上到了
- Kate... - Castle, just stay with me. We're almost there.
你好  布拉德·帕克  我来采访
Hi. Brad Parker. Here for the interview.
里德夫人在等你
Mrs. Reed's expecting you.
谢谢
Thank you.
国防部长里德办公室  有什么事
Defense Secretary Reed's office. How can I help you?
打扰  里德夫人
Excuse me, Mrs. Reed.
这位是帕克先生
Mr. Parker.
谢谢  朱莉
Thanks, Julie.
请坐  帕克先生
Please, make yourself comfortable, Mr. Parker.
谢谢  夫人
Thank you, ma'am.
我能给你倒点茶吗
Can I pour you some tea?
如果你有的话
Well, only if you're having some.
当然有
That's a deal.
要糖吗
Do you take sugar?
你打通了里德一家
You've reached the Reeds.
我们现在不能接电话  请留言
We're not available, so please leave a message...
-该死  -我们会及时回电
- Come on. Damn it. - And your call will be returned promptly.
-凯特  -不  卡塞尔  看着我
- Kate... - No, Castle, just look at me.
坚持住  好吗
Just hang on, okay?
快到了
We're almost there.
哦不  卡塞尔
Castle. No.
里克  看着我  好吗
No. Rick, look at me, will you?
里德夫人
Mrs. Reed?
她没反应  叫救护车
She's not responding. Send an ambulance.
-她断气了  -帕克  放下电话
- She's not breathing. - Parker, drop the phone.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
解药在哪儿  帕克
Where's the antidote, Parker?
-放下武器  -他给里德夫人下毒了
- Lower your weapon. - He poisoned Mrs. Reed.
陪着她
Stay with her.
都结束了  帕克
It's over, Parker!
我们知晓了一切
We know everything.
趁还来得及  把解药给我们
Now give us the antidote before it's too late.
-不  等等  -里德下令时  等了吗
- No, wait. - Did Reed wait when he ordered the strike?
不  他没有  现在该让他尝尝这滋味了
No. No, now it's his turn to see how it feels.
她会死的  就像法拉赫一样
She's gonna die... just like Farrah.
求你了
Please.
帕克  不只她一人被你下毒
Parker, she's not the only one that you've poisoned.
我的未婚夫要死了  他需要解药
My fiance's dying. He needs that antidote.
不  你不懂
No, you don't understand.
太迟了
Too late.
It's too late.
你最好是错的
You better hope you're wrong.
卡塞尔
Castle?
我做了一个超奇怪的梦  你在
I had the strangest dream, and you were there.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank god.
嗨  老爸
Hi, dad.
你也在  你也在
Hey, you were there, and you were there.
嘿  C先生
Hey, Mr. C.
我给你做灵气治疗了
I did some healing reiki on you.
看来起作用了
Looks like it worked.
你也在
And you were there.
他会没事的
I think he's gonna be all right.
多亏了你
Yeah, thanks to you.
好啦
Well, look, look,
我们让他们独处一会儿
why don't we--why don't we give you guys a moment?
走吧
Come on.
-需要我们的话  我们就在外面  -好
- We'll be outside if you need us. - Okay.
爱你
Love you.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
你的周末怎么样
How was your weekend?
挺平淡的  你的呢
You know, uneventful. Yours?
一样
Same.
但我至少见到你了
But at least I got to see you.
真抱歉  卡塞尔
I'm so sorry, Castle.
一切本不应该这么艰难的
This wasn't supposed to be this hard.
你是指华盛顿的工作还是我们的感情
What, Washington or us?
有时候
Sometimes...
生活中最困难的是
the hardest things in life...
值得做的事
are the things most worth doing.
就因为我们还没找到解决办法
Just because we haven't figured it out yet
并不代表我们找不到
doesn't mean we won't.
不过告诉你
Tell you what, though.
下次说想死我了
Next time I say I'm dying to see you,
最好保持在比喻的情况下
let's keep it metaphoric.
好的
Deal.
他怎么样
How's he doing?
考虑到一切  还好
He's okay, considering.
里德夫人怎么样
What about Mrs. Reed?
她会没事的
Uh, she will pull through.
里德部长呢
And what about Secretary Reed?
他会怎样处置
What's gonna happen with him?
什么意思
What do you mean?
他为了保全自己隐瞒了信息
He withheld information to save his own ass.
有人因此死掉
People almost died because of it.
事情没那么简单
Well, we both know it's not that simple.
至少会展开
Well... there's gonna be an investigation,
调查吧
at least, right?
你想让一切都黑白分明  我明白
You... want everything to be black or white. I get it.
但在华府
But... in this town,
事情总是处在灰色地带  做这份工作
it rarely is, and to do this job,
你得去接受这一点
you have to make peace with that.
但是
But hey...
帕克会对里德夫人下手  真是超赞的判断
That was a hell of a hunch about Mrs. Reed.
你该为自己骄傲
You should feel really good about this.
那是卡塞尔的想法
Yeah, well, that was Castle.
但是你很明智地按直觉行动
But you were smart enough to act on it.
那是你的判断
That was your call.
而你在不知道我怎么行动的情况下就后援了
And you backed me up without even knowing my play.
那是搭档该做的
That's what partners do.
是啊
Yeah.
那是搭档该做的
That's what partners do.